To me, spiritualism is a very fundamental word
对我来说，灵修是教师职业中
within the teaching profession
一个非常基本的词，
even though it's one that raises certain
尽管它在我们的社会中
fears rightfully so in our society.
引起了某些理所当然的恐惧。
We do have a separation of church and state.
我们确实有教会和国家的分裂现象。
And there's nothing about the work we're doing
我们所做的工作并没有
that violates that rightful wall of separation
违反那堵合法的隔离墙，
were not prepounding increed
我们不是在宣传信条教义
doctrine or anybody's particular view
或任何人的特殊观点，
we're creating situations in which
我们是在创造人们可以
people can listen to their own inner truth.
倾听自己内心真相的环境。
However they understand that and
不管他们如何理解，
however they have framed that,
也不管他们如何构思，
in teaching, spirituality means to me that
在教学中，灵性对我来说意味着
you understand yourself to be not an autonomous agent,
你理解自己不是一个自主的代理人，
not performing in front of folks,
不是在人们面前表演，
but a weaver of connections.
而是一个联系的编织者。
That the spirituality is
灵性是关于
about this desire to be connected with
与比我自己的自我更大的东西
something larger than my own ego.
相联系的渴望。
And in teaching that translates into the desire
在教学中，
to be connected with to my students,
这转化为与我的学生、
to the communities from which they come to
与他们所来自的社区、
the lives they lead and
与他们所过的生活以及
to the subject I'm teaching.
与我所教的科目相联系的渴望。
The courage to teach has a great deal to do with honoring
教学勇气在很大程度上与尊重该学科有关，
that subject as if it were a person giving it
就像它是一个人一样，
as much status and standing and dignity
给予它尽可能多的地位、身份和尊严，
as one would hope you we would give each other.
就像人们希望我们互相给予对方地位、身份、尊严一样。
Because when you can establish that subject
因为当你能把这个学科确立为
as a part of the ecosystem of people's lives,
人们生活中生态系统的一部分，
a part of this web of connectedness
作为灵性生活一直在
that the spiritual life is always trying to weave,
努力编织的这个联系网的一部分时，
then you've got students in a relation to the subject
那么你就会让学生与该学科建立起一种关系，
that's going to lead to learning.
从而导致学习的发生。